appearance concerns “dress to impress” when we honestly analyze the true rearing, isn’t tells us to dress to deceive, 
pretend to grandstand a farce. It’s clearly gays lie, lie, lie, to everyone we come on contact with.  Another rain Secret of life, 
is never tell lies, and perform a never lying again rebirth, practice to stop telling any form of lies for a day, then a week , 
month, and next thing you would realize its years has pass by not telling lies. There isn’t a single reason to tell a lie. The first 
question a master liar would definitely ask what if you have to tell a lie to save your life. You would have to get more of the 
back story for the answer to these questions, later on in this eugenic fantasy, in order words, "wait for it." primitivism Root 
cause, linchpins None had reset their minds to desire less There are no reasons to lie. lies are used to deceive people, cause an 
unhealthy departure from your innocence Live clean and all inclusive, only then Υοu'RE mind and cosmic life force will truly 
prosper. "Hi Mac," she greeted when I went inside. She was at the ancient Mr. Coffee machine, attempting to coax the 
temperamental old fart to life. I couldn’t have cared less whether the infernal thing worked or not because I wasn’t a coffee 
drinker. I wasn’t about to spend any money on a new one. Still, it was comical to watch Jennifer as she attempted to bitch
slapped Mr. Coffee to life. Sometimes this place has rewards. And you can’t put a price on that. We are pursuing love, 
excellence, prosperity, property, etc., in a permanent state of blended unnecessariness that has Spiraling to rock bottom. 
Most of us are a molten fusion brimming with unnecessary grievances, stress, and frustrations, without Selflessness, and 
"pathological friendliness". Pursuing anything relevant without proper levels of consciousness is the basic recipe for chaos. Most 
of us are progress rapidly with queed gone wild, and prominent selfishness into eloping brinkmanship. Seeking acquaintance, 
friendship, love, marriage, when both parties were encourages to promote, and following the money, power, fame, and status, 
desperately seeking "embarrassing amount of riches, "by all means necessary," inevitably must end very bad, we had decided 
to deal in in appearance, and agrees to be endow with a ful blast of thoughtlessness, recklessness, carelessness, while growing 
more and more devoid of admitting our faults. We would some way along the way sell, or exchange our freedom for primitive 
money fame, power of status, only able to offer to the world a shell of our truth potential. Most of the world population is 
motivated by money, power, and fame, its normal that "the fortune of most is precipitated by the misfortune of others". I 
did my best to keep a poker face and not show that I was panicked. I stood in a point position just DE Sensitivity rises, etc. 
one of our main purpose of life is the freewill to extend creative energy to our desire change are a complete was of time, and 
is just subjecting each other to unnecessary feat. All Inclusive change Ismare's, interfere with freewill, compromise the 
greater good, unravel out psychic, stuck, bog down in quick sand, There are billions of manufactures crooked-up dead foods, to 
highjack by our unsuspecting senses, devious aromas, suspicious taste, well composed sights, covert smells and clandestine 
sounds. Reminder, trouble always had an intriguing deceptive air, unnatural look, too good to be true taste and suspicious 
qreat smell. I hoped we had made the right decision. I wasn’t sure how my parents would react to Maddy and I taking the 
kids to the Gertie Machine’s vault. I was pretty sure they wouldn’t like it. I just didn’t see any other alternative. I smiled 
and nodded. The following day Chris was asked to take both vehicles out and to get to know the area. The very first thing he 
did was to promote one of the two locals he had been allocated, as his guide. Chris nick named him Paddy and ordered him to 
sit up front with him at all times. Choosing Paddy as his guide rather than the other local, because his English was very good. 
Chris Weeded Somebody who spoke good clear English. If a firefight was to develop the last thing, he needed was to keep 
repeating himself. Once Old Tom told him a story of and earlier London Street entertainer who used a post Office mail bag in 
his act. These bags were made up of a very close tight weave, that would not allow daylight to pass through. The entertainer 
would then be seen to place a few rats into the bag. He would then Stick his head in side of the bag and suddenly appear with a 
rat in his mouth, having grabbed it at the back of its neck. He ended the story by telling him that he used the same principle. 
I chuckled "priests don't keep score of good deeds. Neither does God. It’s what’s in our hearts that counts." This is also a 
virtual how to begin to, "cast healing light, through the dense darkness steeped in unnecessary", "manifold wickedness". That can 
aid in removing and preventing obstacles preventing, "intense happiness ambiance", with grand hope in setting the stage to 
developing, an all inclusive, and collective fest drift "paradigm shift". Sense aren’t common, common sense is highly based on 
serendipitous life lesson, an individual are fortunate to be privileged , depending on their priorities. Common Sense is like a drawing 
from a deck of cards, you never can know what you're going to get. The universe has always being out super best 
incomparably beyond and above us all "teacher. Everywhere our universe has been setting the perfect bar none boundless 
love, kindness, how to experience "joy in the fullness" behavioral ingenuities, generous accommodations, optimum character 
building and structuring, "predictive modeling, "crystal clear and sharp understanding, culminating into supreme prime 
directives, motions. Gaps are traditional, and are available to protect corner of our longest running accepted idiosyncrasies. These
are just some of the infinite lingering remnants, from routine mi' programming, and endless twisted priorities.From a 
sesquipedalianist in the impotence red situation room, also known as existence, normal rules of exchange, interaction do not 
apply if we restructure our levels of consciousness, and perceptions, to all inclusive and collective favor, Life is a future concept,
every split waking and sleeping second, we constantly moving forward into the future. Out levels of consciousness has been 
compromised before we are even born, begin the mesmerizing journey of life. All of our normal systematic ways of life, are 
super fortified in place for us to observe, experience, and "live out our entire lives twistedly primitive, through teat view 
mirrors, keeping us stuck to the past, while life are an onward and forward concepts." She didn’t answer. She didn’t look at 
me, either. It was if I wasn’t even there. This is chance to recognize the world has lot perspectives, and didn’t learn from 
reckless leaders. Here the thing, what is an aftermath contingency, and like all aftermath contingencies, they are always are relief 
and a systematic ploy to get more funding, an escalating blow back part of the problem. "Then Ducky will deal with 
him". Every has their own personal brand, bout with secret pain "I thought it was you who had me in your clutches." There
